I've generated over $100 million with
cold email and here is my exact text
stack for 2025 Everything Has Changed
this year how do we crush it what is our
exact Tech stack to ensure
deliverability right
[Music]
now if you've looked at any of my videos
over the past couple years you've seen
how much things have changed first I
went viral for my original cold email
template back in 2017 then we wrote the
book on cold email but what works now
because cold email is not like Facebook
ads and anybody who says it is
fundamentally misunderstands the
platform you're not spending $300 and
getting a meeting with cold email cold
email is more like those letters that
you receive in the mail I can sit here
with a straight face and tell you that I
can guarantee 5,000 cents a month for
whatever a couple hundred dollar a month
and that your target market will see it
and then if you need help with scripting
Etc you can join AB Mastermind where we
talk about it six times a week and we
have dozens and dozens of hours of
courses that tell you exactly what to
write for cold email in 2025 I want you
to memorize one word and that is
infrastructure sounds complicated but
that is where we are as ascending
Society now you have to build a
connection of tools in order to make
sure that your emails hit the inboxes
properly as part of your infrastructure
build we need a few key pieces first we
need a lead pool that's basically a list
of leads then you need a verification
waterfall to find the emails then you'll
need to customize the campaigns send the
emails somehow manage your warm leads as
they come in I'll give you a spoiler
right now the place to go for help is
right where you are right now with me
Alex Perman what is a lead pool this is
a place where leads exist the simplest
and most straightforward one is linked
in sales Navigator in here you can just
search for leads using lead filters pick
your geography or your job titles Etc
and you can find company list
here I also like to use Apollo which is
a lead database and just lets you search
leads very similar to sales Navigator
but more of the data is provided here
whether that data is correct or not
we'll find out later on in this text
stack but you just need a raw list third
place I like to go is builtwith which
lets you search by technology so if you
have a competitor that is installed on
people's websites let's say I'm selling
website design and I only want to build
for people that have WordPress websites
I can just type in WordPress here and
builtwith will give me a list of all the
URL of every website on the internet
that has WordPress and I can just
download that lead list here 33 million
currently active websites with WordPress
or if you're more specific you can go
with any sort of front-facing tool let's
say you want to Target HubSpot customers
they're all here on built with so now
you have your list of leads but we need
to make sure that the emails are
legitimate and for that we're going to
use a verification waterfall instead of
putting all of these logos in here like
findy mail or data mg or Hunter all I'm
going to do is say use clay because in
clay all you have to do is Click add
enrichment type in the word waterfall
and hit this work email button and built
for you is this list now of course
you're going to want to use apis instead
of clay credits but if you want more
info on that check out my clay video for
lead verification we'll use clay using
this stack of tools now if you've read
my book cold email Manifesto you know I
love custom cold email campaigns writing
pitches writing custom first lines etc
etc now you can still do this manually
but you can also use clay for this and
Clay has a perfect integration with chat
GPT here I'm using it to find the niche
to find the ideal client profile who the
biggest competitors are writing an
amazing idea finding a childhood story
that the customer might relate to their
biggest fear as an entrepreneur their
mission so there's a ton of stuff that
you can use GPT for and it plugs right
into clay for customization we're going
to use clay and chat gbt to send the
cold email themselves my favorite tool
is smart lead. smart lead is very
similar to what I used to use with
instantly except it's more up to date so
for sending the emails I like smart lead
now there's one step we're missing here
which is how do you set up the inboxes
themselves for this I recommend joining
the ab Mastermind because we have our
own setup that we use but otherwise I'll
just put custom SMTP here you can find a
bunch of providers out here if you just
Google custom SMTP for cold email
there's a ton of them my specific
recommendation is to join The Mastermind
and you can use ours that we use
internally otherwise there's a ton of
them out there and they're all varying
qualities so I don't want to recommend
anyone except ours if you want this one
go to Alex burman.com Mastermind and you
can join it and only as a mastermind
member can you get this custom SMTP set
up and it's only a couple hundred bucks
a month and it ensures deliverability
then once the leads are coming in you're
going to want to manage those warm leads
using a CRM and for that I like .c I
also don't mind just putting everything
into a Google sheet and then you can
just warm call and warm text the leads
as they come in so this is the cold
email stack for 2025 exactly what's
working right this second you can
screenshot this and you can use this if
you need any help of course just contact
me you can reply to this video that
you're seeing or you can just join the
ab Mastermind and I'll help you
one-on-one to set this up in a second
I'll share with you another interesting
video smash that like button and I'll
talk to you in a second to a strong 2025